this is this is Zakir from Prudential
Singapore Opex team uh basically Opex
has a Consulting Academy and uh Coe and
I'm part of the Coe uh Cy team leading
the intelligent automation piece of it
so our team is basically uh with a group
of professionals who are specialized in
driving improvement and optimization
across different departments in
Singapore and our team is also typically
includes
individuals with a range of skills and
expertise including data scientists ml
Engineers automation Engineers process
improvements and and and and the lean
Six Sigma exports also uh are part of
our team
and and when it comes to the uh major
goal of our team is to drive a
continuous Improvement across the
organization resulting in improved
efficiency uh increased productivity and
most importantly focusing on the
enhanced uh customer satisfaction
okay so as as an organization uh
prudentials mission is to make lives
better by solving the financial
challenges of our changing world we also
aim to help individuals and families
Achieve Financial Security and Peace of
Mind by providing a range of financial
products and services including life
insurance retirement planning and
investment management
I should thank uh bloopism for giving us
this opportunity yeah and uh coming to
the solution The Claim Solution that we
have built is I mean I call it as one of
the best example to showcase the power
of intelligent Automation and its
ability to uh Drive business value and
transform the way we work
we are particularly proud on the impact
that our solution has had on our
organization and the customers by
significantly reducing the time and
resources required to process claims
while improving accuracy and efficiency
yeah so we have been able to provide a
better experience for our customers and
increase their trust in our organization
along with that collaboration was also a
key to the success of the solution we
worked closely with our claims team to
develop and implement this this solution
in a very short time this collaborative
approach ensured that the solution was
aligned with our organization's goals
and was able to deliver real business
value this was designed in such a way
that it can be easily scalable and
replicated across different departments
and business units by saving a lot of
development efforts this award would not
only be a a testament to our team's hard
work and dedication but would also
Inspire us to continue to strive for uh
to strive for excellence in all aspects
of our customer interactions moreover
being nominated for this award would
enhance our reputation also in the
industry and among our customers
demonstrating that we are a company that
truly cares about delivering the best
possible experiences with digital
transformations
we are really grateful for this
recognition and will we will use it as a
motivation to continue to provide
exceptional customer service in the
future and yeah so this is a very big uh
achievement for us